Guide to the Eyes of Texas television show episodes and summaries collection, 1978-2009 MS 170
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- 1990 episodes, 226747
  - April 21, 1990: Texas State Aquarium, Corpus Christi / R. Hensz-Grapefruit King, Weslaco / Red Hanks-Rattlesnakes, Yoakum-1980 / 'The Cradle' DRT, Galveston, 226768 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 456)
  - April 28, 1990: Turkeys in East Texas, Lufkin / Cherokee Chief Bowles, Neches / Sunken Dolls-North Carolina-Texas / Star Drug STore, Galveston / Cedar Park to Kingsland, 226767 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 457)
  - May 05, 1990: Cecil Franklin-Blues, Nacogdoches / Glen Climer Rummage Barn, Poteet / Davis/Cook-Reconstruction Governors / Adkins-Group Model Train, Spring / Willow City Loop, 226766 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 458)
  - May 12, 1990: 'Dancing Tom' Davis, La Grange / Tideland Issue &Texas Politics / Liz Carpenter-"Johnsons Of Johnson City" / Uncertain, Texas-Caddo Lake, 226765 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 459)
  - May 19, 1990: English Telephone booths, Roan's Prarie / Don Kelly-Postcard Colleciton, Beaumont / Mysterios "Lubbock Lights" / Prarie Pete Park-Odessa-1979 / Ledbetter, Texas, 226764 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 460)
  - May 26, 1990: Seymour Furniture Restorers, Beaumont / Rockland, Texas / Leopold Stokowski-Houston Symphony / Scott Costa-Knoves, Spicewood / 'Summer Mummers', Midland, 226763 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 461)
  - June 02, 1990: San Jacinto Flag Restored / Diablos Baseball, El Paso / Henry Smith, Kentucky to Texas / Craig Carter-Cowboy Singer, Big Bend, 226762 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 462)
  - Sep. 22, 1990: Carpenter, Boling - the Second Armored Division, Fort Hood / Hockersmith, Anderson - Union Carbide Volunteers, Texas City / El Camiono Real/King's Highway, first report, Natchitoches, LA / Matthews, Klein - Sauer-Beckmann Farm, Texas Hill Country, 226761 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 463)
  - Sep. 29. 1990: Williams - Save the Oaks Project, Plum / Barker - Eldorado Blanket Factory, Woolen Mills / El Camino Real, second report, Alto / Appelt, Schwab - German "Good Ol' Boys" open a Restaurant and Biergarten, 226760 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 464)
  - Oct. 6, 1990: Bates - Portable Sawmill Operator, Chireno / Holmes - Laundromat, Azle / El Camino Real, third report, Normangee / King William District, San Antonio, 226759 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 465)
  - Oct. 13, 1990: Shepperd, Hill - Stonehenge II, Hunt / Montgomery - Lightcrust Doughboys, Fort Worth / El Camino Real, fourth report, Fort Tenoxtitlan / Rhyne, Johnson - Balmorhea Pool, West Texas, 226758 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 466)
  - Oct 20, 1990: Crater of Diamonds State Park, Arkansas / Hybner - St Mary's Catholic Church, Victoria / Joe Smith - El Camino Real, fifth report, Caldwell / Joe Don Scott - Rink Necked Pheasants, Texas Panhandle, 226757 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 467)
  - Oct. 27, 1990: Tippe, Mahony, Clare, Dujka - Fort Bend Opry, Rosenberg / Roberson - Dr. Bob's Chuck Wagon Gang, Levelland / El Camino Real, sixth report / Nacogdoches / Monzingo, Hinds - San Felipe Springs, Del Rio, 226756 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 468)
  - Nov. 03, 1990: Lester Meier-Travling Rodeo, Fredericksburg / Wm Brooks-Junk Man, Pisgah / Tragedy-San Saba, Menard / Whooping Cranes, Aransas Refuge / Cullen Home, San Augustine, 226755 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 469)
  - Nov 10, 1990: Terlingua Medics Service / Apelt Armadillo Farm, Comfort / El Camino Real / Monte Verdi Plantation, Cushing, 226754 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 470)
  - Nov. 17, 1990: Archaeological Trip to Utopia / Gus Roesler-Woodcarver, Woodbranch / Dunsavage-New York Cheesecake, Baxter / Old Fort Stockton, 226753 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 471)
  - Nov. 24, 1990: Kokernot Field, Alpine / Bonnie Parker-Clyde Barrow, Dallas / New Hope Church, Cedar Park / Republic of Texas Boundary Marker, 226752 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 472)
  - Dec 01, 1990: Benson-Bird Sound Library, College Station / Jerry Witte-Baseball Star, Houston / Valentine, Texas / French Legation/Creole Kitchen, Austin, 226751 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 473)
  - Dec. 08, 1990: Huff/Smith Diary - Part 1 / Huff/Smith Diary - Part 2 / Dub & Delela Haley, Marathon / Wild Basin Preserve, Austin, 226750 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 474)
  - Dec. 15, 1990: Aldridge Sawmill, Zavalla / Bradbury, Hancock, Hopkins, Coleman Clark - Provident City / Fort Mason and the Second Cavalry / Warren and Roberta Lynch, Study Butte, 226749 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 475)
  - Dec. 22, 1990 (Christmas Special): Hall, Freeman - Hill Country Christmas (part I), Lakeway / Hill Country Christmas (part 2) / Christmas Montage, Yoakum, Jefferson / Encore Youth Performers, Galveston, 226748 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 476)
- 1991 episodes, 226713
  - KPRC's summary of 1991 episodes, 226746 (Folder 14)
  - Jan. 5, 1991: Blonde Calderon profile, Del Rio / Wendl, Wright - Old Service Station Gets a New Look, Corpus Christi / Cardwell - Fish Rubbing, Austin / Krauter - Inguenhuet Store, Comfort, 226745 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 477)
  - Jan. 12, 1991: Jim Levelle - Oswald's Protector, Dallas / Alfalfa Bill Murray, Toadsuck / Japanese Sunken Garden, San Antonio / Kidd, Kemp - Friday mountain Camp, Driftwood / Casterline, Hall, Garza - The Texas Maritime Museum, Rockport, 226744 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 478)
  - Jan. 19, 1991: Pope - 1896 Lunchroom at the Driscoll Hotel, Austin / Burdick - Rosanky Auto Museum, Rosanky / Hunter, Carsillo, Peal, Chapman - Wax Museum Artists, Grand Prairie / Reynolds, Long - The Million Barrel Oil Musum, Monahans, 226743 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 479)
  - Jan. 26, 1991: Dorfman - Union Depot Buliding, El Paso / Wilson, Harrison, Dunning, Ward - Young Audiences of Houston / Puppeteers Rose and Fred Knapp, Fredericksburg / Baker, Todd - Wells Branch Homestead, Austin, 226742 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 480)
  - Feb. 09, 1991: Walking Tour-Historic Flatonia / Palafox-Webb County / Governors Ma & Pa Ferguson / Mo Ranch Museum, Hunt, 226741 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 481)
  - Feb. 23, 1991: Mill Store Plaza, New Braunfels / Michael Moss-Furniture Maker, Grapetown / Theodore Gentilz-TX History artist / Old Emporium, Galveston, 226740 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 482)
  - March 02, 1991: Bastile Days-Paris, TX / Vice President John Nance Garner, Uvalde / Cele & Richland in Travis Co., WPA Post Office Art-60 Towns, 226739 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 483)
  - March 09, 1991: Texas Wild Rice, San Marcos / Jim Rantala-Windor Chairs, Heights / Buck Newsome-Border Patrol, El Paso / Bordertown, Farwell, 226738 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 484)
  - March 16, 1991: Women's AirForce Service Corps-1 / WASP - Part 2 / Lauren Barker-Mini Portraits, Austin / Stockyards B&B, Fort Worth, 226737 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 485)
  - March 23, 1991: Don Starns-Juke Box Repair, Channelview / Handbook of Texas, Austin/Lockhart / Koffee Kupp Restaurant, Wells / Story of Indian Emily-Fort Davis, 226736 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 486)
  - March 30, 1991: Anita Pitchford-History Teacher, Turkey / Glen Bowen-Fountain Pens, Houston / Bob Willoughby-Jalapenos, Uvalde / Vicker's Inn, La Porte, 226735 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 487)
  - April 06, 1991: Floyd Spurgeon-Rocking Chairs, Huffman / Legend-Brushy Bill Roberts, Hico / Texas Basket Co., Jacksonville / Jacul Dugout, Big Bend, 226734 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 488)
  - April 13, 1991: Geo Springer-Music Man, Montalba / Kirkley House Moved to Warren / Rogers Hornsby-Baseball, Winters / Gruene Texas, 226733 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 489)
  - April 20, 1991: Craig Cameron-Horse Trainer, Fulshear / Gladys Strong-Shell Art, Wimberley / John Rinehart-Studebakers, Singleton / Dessau Hall, Pflugerville, 226732 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 490)
  - April 27, 1991: Klinger's-Village Dime Store, Houston / German Festival, Klein / Black Film Archives, Dallas/Tyler / Caddo Indian Museum, Longview, 226731 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 491)
  - May 04, 1991: Lose Your Buns for Funds, Gonzales / Timer/House Raising, Nacogdoches / Lucy Maukof-Cactus, Sterling city / Fire Department Museum, Houston, 226730 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 492)
  - May 11, 1991: Nelson Merrell, Round Rock / Ben & Jess Rowley-Woodwork, Port Neches / Ernest Lord-Architech, Navasota / Dr. Pepper Plant, Dublin, 226729 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 493)
  - May 18, 1991: Alfred Poindexter-Vet, Prairie View / Rice Hotel History, Houston / Harold Conner-RR Buff, Fort Worth / The Beauty of Texas, Pflugerville, 226728 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 494)
  - May 25, 1991: Gov. Bill & Vera Daniel, Waco / Roy Pate-Mini Horses, Longview / DC-Deputy Cat, Kermit - 1987 / Mimosa Hall-B&B, Karnack, 226727 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 495)
  - June 01, 1991: Longhorn Cavern-CCC 854, Burnet / Bobby Jones-Polka King, Bay City / Charlie Sifford-Golfer, Kingwood / Indianola/Matagorda History, 226726 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 496)
  - June 08, 1991: Crawford-Pecan Art, Shady Shores / A.D. Eversole's Barber Shop, Richmond / Randy Worely-Sculptor, Austin / Wendish Museum, Serbin - Lee Co., 226725 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 497)
  - Sept. 21 1991: Outlaw/Lawmen Assn., El Paso / Kirk Alyn-'48 Superman, Woodlands / Canine Office Bill, Houston / Texola, OK - Glen Rio, NM, Route 66, 226724 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 498)
  - Sept. 28, 1991: Carter - Newspaper Museum, Alto / Jumbo Hamilton-San Jacinto Club, Houston / Rt. 66-Shamrock - Part 1 / Rt. 66-Shamrock - Part 2, 226723 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 499)
  - Oct. 12, 1991: Polo on the Prairie, Albany / Rt. 66 - Mc Lean, Texas / Donna Demers-Mail Carrier, New Waverly / Gaatesville Church-County Museum, 226722 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 500)
  - Oct. 19, 1991: May - McGilvray-Theater/Home / Barfield-Orchids, Corpus Christi / Carter - Roote 66 - Alanreed / Blue Grass Festival, Glen Rose, 226721 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 501)
  - Oct. 26, 1991: Mahan, Vocechia - Lobo-Ghost Town for Sale / Route 66-Groom, Ruby Denton / Hickey-Famous Water, Mineral Wells / Model T Meet, Hill Country, 226720 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 502)
  - Nov. 02, 1991: Gonzales, Huse - Shopping Escapes, Jacksonville / Jernigan's Village, Hebron / Junior Miller-Arrowhead Maker, Gustine / Route 66-Jericho & Conway, 226719 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 503)
  - Nov. 11, 1991: John Wesley Hardin, El Paso / Route 66 - Amarillo / Spinney-Woodcarver, Beaumont / Thanksgiving Square, Dallas, 226718 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 504)
  - Nov. 16, 1991: Texas Books for Blind, Midland / Creech - SF Austin Arboretum, Nacogdoches / Art on Library Walls, Jones Creek / Roote 66 - Golden Cafe, Amarillo, 226717 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 505)
  - Nov. 23, 1991: Hawk Watch, Corpus Christi / Route 66 - Bushland / David Renfro-Gords, Zavalla / Carnegie Library, Ballinger, 226716 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 506)
  - Nov. 30, 1991: TX Horned Toad, West Texas / Route 66 - Wildorado / Schaffer Observatory, Schulenburg 1 / Shaffer Observatory, Schulenburg 2, 226715 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 507)
  - Dec. 21, 1991: Monarch Butterfly Migration / Route 66 - Vega / Ace Reid-Cowboy Cartoons, Kerrville / B. Ainsworth-Music Boxes, Fluvanna, 226714 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 508)
- 1992 episodes, 226672
  - KPRC's summary of 1992 episodes, 226712 (Folder 15)
  - Jan. 04, 1992: Santa Claus Robbery-1927, Cisco / Route 66 - Adrian / Eugene Clark Library, Lickhart / Hamburger Cookoff, Athens, 226711 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 509)
  - Jan. 11, 1992: Greyhound Adoption, Riesel / Route 66 -Glen Rio / Mrs. Williams Grave, Stephens Co. / Dinosaur Flats, Canyon Lake, 226710 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 510)
  - Jan. 18, 1992: Cozart - Goat Dog, Cisco / Sidewalk Cattlemen's Asoociation, Madisonville / Crafts Lady Odess Jones, Throcmorton / Route Sixty Six, Part 14, Bull Canyon, 226709 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 511)
  - Jan. 25, 1992: Dan Kalenax-Ben Franklin, Odessa / Route 66 - Texas Panhandle / Texas Cajuns, Jefferson Co. / Moody Mansion, Galveston, 226708 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 512)
  - Feb. 01, 1992: Huntsville Revitilization-R. Haas / Oliver Loving- Rancher / Sandstone Quarry, Barstow / TX Sports Hall of Champions, Waco, 226707 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 513)
  - Feb. 08, 1992: Upshaw - Reviving Roby & Northern RR / Swett, Miller - Primarily Primate, Leon Springs / History of Mentone, Loving Co. / New Zion BBQ, Huntsville, 226706 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 514)
  - Feb. 15, 1992: Elite Cafe & The Circle, Waco / Connell House, Stanton-Martin Co. / Oscar Holcomb, Houston / Rio Grande Trail, Brownsville-Laredo, 226705 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 515)
  - Feb. 22, 1992: WWII Camp Howze Reunion, Gainesville / 'Bill the Shooter', Breckenridge / Lipton Tea Church, Texas City / Sterquell Wagons/Carriages, Amarillo, 226704 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 516)
  - Feb. 29, 1992: Kitchen's Hardware/Deli, Mineola / 1st Calvery Detachment, Fort Hood / Claudia Deborah-Chair Caner, Beamont / Quarter Horse Museum, Amarillo, 226703 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 517)
  - March 07, 1992: Jim Keeter-Tree Expert, San Antonio / Barbed Wire-Devil's Rope Museum, McLean / Movies of the Alamo / Show Close, 226702 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 518)
  - March 14, 1992: Pig Stand Diner, Houston & More / Robertsons-TX Confederate Generals / Bierre's-Puzzel Makers, Heights / Pittsburg Heritage Museum, 226701 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 519)
  - March 21, 1992: Houston St. John's School Field Trip / John Pickering-Buddy Holly Backup Singer / Father Chat-Soldier/Priest, Galveston / Houston Police Department Museum, 226700 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 520)
  - March 28, 1992: 4-16-1947 Texas City Disaster 1 / 4-16-1947 Texas City Disaster 2 / L.P. Vosscamp-Hourse Plow, Richmond / Jeff. Davis Mem. Highway-Orange to El Paso, 226699 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 521)
  - April 04, 1992: Endangered Brown Pelican, S. Padre / Schoolhouse Coop, Coldspring / Chuck Wagon Cookoff, Fort Davis / Prairie Dogs, Snyder & Lubbock, 226698 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 522)
  - April 11, 1992: Dot's Place-Finest Cook, Cherokee Co. / Roger Moore-Hyde Tanner, Lometa / Castolon Compound, Big Bend / Matagorda-Town & Exclusive Lodge / Wildflowers, Central Texas, 226697 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 523)
  - April 18, 1992: S Tucker-The Brick Oven, Kempner / Scott Birdwell-Beer Maker, Houston / Dinosaur Garden, Moscow / Carousel Company, Wimberley / East Texas Dogwood Trail, 226696 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 524)
  - April 25, 1992: David Liindsey, Texas Author / Leslie Mizell-Furniture Maker, Cleveland / Ann Whitney 1835-1867, Hamilton / New Spain Exhibit, Houston, 226695 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 525)
  - May 02, 1992: Mine Reclaimation, San Jacinto Co. / Ada O'Connor-Candymaker, Florence / James Kanak-Cushmans, Rosenberg / Wilbur-"Ideal Pottery", Dallas, 226694 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 526)
  - May 09, 1992: Leefty Frizzell Memorial, Corsicana / C M Sanders-German Heritage Artist / Don Hunter-Grapette Coll., Friendswood / KofC "Santa Maria" Replica, Bay City, 226693 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 527)
  - May 16, 1992: "The Moods"-Rock n Roll Band / Ashbel Smith-TX Legation, London / Lefty Christopher-Windmills, Monahans / Art of Shingle Splitting, Woodville, 226692 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 528)
  - May 23, 1992: Texas State Cemetery, Austin / Cherokee Theater Renovation, Rusk/ Darrell Lister-Bee Buster, Bellaire / Catarina - The Town & Old Hotel (Royal Palm), 226691 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 529)
  - May 30, 1992: Hendee-Taste of Texas, Houston / Evergreen Cemetery, Houston / John Grivich-Bluebird Man, Huntsville / Overstreet-Neches River Tour, 226690 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 530)
  - June 06, 1992: Broussard's Crawfish, Nome / El Paso Salt War- 1877 / Fincastle Farms -PYO, Larue / Tower of Life Building, San Antonio, 226689 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 531)
  - June 13, 1992: Red Cockaded Woodpecker, Coldspring / Briscoe Hunting Lodge, Catarina / Frank Bros Salvage Yard, Houston / J Brown-Stagecoaches, Weatherford, 226688 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 532)
  - Sept. 19, 1992: K Wingo-Master Potter, Marshall / Graham's-Route 66 Momentoes, Stratford / Bartell-Bird Rescue, Rio Grand Valley / Muller-Peach Harvest, Fredericksburg, 226687 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 533)
  - Sept. 26, 1992: Ken Law - Fish Lures, Tye / Bea's Steakhouse, Anson / Fischner-Dinosaur Artist, Needville / Antique Business, Gladewater, 226686 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 534)
  - Oct. 03, 1992: Cowboys Songs/Stories, Big Spring / Mariposa Park-Sculptures, Corpus Christi / Dr. Henz-Grapefruit King, Weslaco / Fort Martin Scott, Fredericksburg, 226685 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 535)
  - Oct. 10, 1992: Black Bears, Big Bend / Bishop Family Antiques, Hawkins / Hugh Scott-Restors Furniture, Houston / Texas State Fair, 226684 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 536)
  - Oct. 17, 1992: Panhandle Suceding from Texas / Jim Wing-Houston Pioneer / J Henry-Saddle Maker, Benchley / St. John's - Book Fair, Houston / Ada Davis - Pig Lady, San Marcos, 226683 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 537)
  - Oct. 24, 1992: Davis'-Taste of Texas Deli, Austin / Pee Wee Keller-Doll Maker, Lake Buchanan / Oldest Cabin-Panhandle, Canyon / Crator of Diamonds State Park-AR, 226682 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 538)
  - Oct. 31, 1992: Don Kenny-3D Art, San Angelo / 1961-NASA Came to Houston / Robert Bruno-House Sculpture, Lubbock / RR-Texas Limited, Galveston-Houston, 226681 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 539)
  - Nov. 07, 1992: New Hope Chruch Outing, Cedar Park / G. Reyes-Guitar Maker, Gregory / Fort Grierson History, Big Lake / TX State Railroad-Rusk - Palestine, 226680 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 540)
  - Nov. 14, 1992: Lou & Don-Chair Caners, Smithville / Fort Bend Opry, Rosenberg / Lucille McFatter-Dolls, Lufkin / RR Hill country Flyer, Cedar Park-Burnet, 226679 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 541)
  - Nov. 21, 1992: Bigbie - Benet Formals, Pittsburg / Sheperd - Stonehenge II, Hunt / Billingsley-Whittler, Onalaska / Tarantula RR Line, Fort Worth, 226678 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 542)
  - Nov. 28, 1992: Ranching Heritage Museum, Lubbock / Kennedy - Pingenot Home, Castroville / Greenhaw Family, Mesquite / Jefferson-Cypress Bayou RR, Jefferson, 226677 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 543)
  - Dec. 05, 1992: TX Challenger RR, Ft Worth-Houston / McFaddin Ward Carriage House, Beaumont / Angle Family Businesses, Knox City / Fort McKavett, Menard, 226676 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 544)
  - Dec. 12, 1992: Stappenbeck - Texas Newspaper Project, Austin / S Revia-Boat builder, Livingston / Dziuk-Popcorn on cob, Hereford / Hummel Museum, New Braunfels, 226675 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 545)
  - Dec. 19, 1992: Ellison - Poinsettia Factory, Brenham / Gibson - Retired Couple doing Craftwork on Lake Limestone / Sheldon - Railroad Artist, Cisco / Toles, Ross - Mercer Aboreteum, Humble, 226674 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 546)
  - Dec. 26, 1992 (Christmas Special): Hall, Freeman - Christmas in the Hill Country, Lakeway / Christmas Around Texas Montage - Bracketville, Yoakum, Fredericksburg, Jefferson, Marshall / Christmas on the Strand with Encore Youth Performers, Galveston, 226673 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 547)
- 1993 episodes, 226667
  - KPRC's summary of 1993 episodes, 226671 (Folder 16)
  - Jan. 2, 1993: Wilkerson, Jacobson, Williams / Tour 18 Golf Course, Humble / Sheffield - Log Home Builder, Wimberley / Montgomery - Remembering the Lightcrust Doughboys / Morris - The Hill Country Steamers Association, 226670 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 548)
  - Jan. 9, 1993 (Copper Canyone Railroad Trip): Cooper Canyon (part 1) - Lajitas, Ojinago, Menonite Community, Divisadero, Creek Town Square, Creel / Copper Canyone (part 2) - El Fuerto, Los Moches, Topolobompo / Don Lanford - Iron Seat Collector, Austin, 226669 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 549)
  - Jan. 16, 1993: Gomez, Blanda, Moore - Scent Chips production, San Antonio / Wiley Robbins profile, Brownwood / Sparks - Ceramic Artist, Tyler / Stillwell, profile, Brewster County, 226668 (Folder -, Episode DVD Episode 550)
- 2007 episodes, 226660
  - KPRC's summary of 2007 episodes, 226666 (Folder 17)
  - March 17, 2007: EOT History w/Ron, Gary & Bill / New Zion BBQ, Huntsville / Bandana Bandit; BJ Reickenbacher, Henderson / Copper Canyon Train Ride, El Paso/Presido / Cave Without a Name, Boerne / Mission Trail Ride, San Antonio / Texas City Disaster - April 1947, 226665 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - June 23, 2007: Project Row Houses, Houston Salt House, Grand Saline / Jimmy Porter, Carrollton / David Mitschke, Loebau / Black Bears, Big Bend / New London School Disaster - March 18, 1937 / Schaper Diary - Last Diary in Galveston / Tee Pee Motel, Wharton, 226664 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - August 25, 2007: Liz Carpenter & The Johnsons, Salado, Blue Bell Creamery's 100th Anniversary, Brenham / Mildred & Floyd Clark, Jefferson / Olivewood Cemetery, Houston / E. O. Goldbeck, San Antonio / Cowboy Breakfasat, Palo Duro Canyon / Military Kids Camp, Bandera / Lost Maples, Vanderpool, 226663 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - Sept. 29, 2007: Spradley Telephone Museum, McGregor Caddo Lake, Uncertain / B-17 Liberty Bell, Huntsville / CP Johnson & His cowdogs, Bastrop / Skeleton Museum, Gatesville / Cantina to Clinic, Houston-Denver Harbor / Cuban Missile Crisis, Houston 1962 / Monarch Butterfly Migration, Marble Falls, 226662 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - Dec. 08, 2007: Dobro / Furniture Maker, Leslie Mizell; Cleveland / The Elissa, Galveston / Windmill Man, Slim Singleton, San Angelo / Whooping Cranes, Auswell / Camp Logan, Houston / Brookwood Community, Brookshire / Fruitcake Factory, Corsicana, 226661 (Folder -, Episode --)
- 2008 episodes, 226654
  - KPRC's summary of 2008 episodes, 226659 (Folder 18)
  - March 28, 2008: Roy Orbison, Wink / Castro in Houston / Bird Banding, Galveston / Babe Aycock, Mayor of Mart / Dance Halls, Cypress / Teas Nursery, Bellaire, History of Bellaire (Centennial) / Mark Dandre-Horseshoer, Bayside, 226658 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - May 30, 2008: Mitzi Riley Trick Rider, Aledo / Bella Karolyi Gymnastics, New Waverly / Texas Olympians, Waco / Babe Didrikson, Beaumont / Ron Stone Obit, Part 1 / Ron Stone Obit, Part 2 / Ron Stone - Travelin' Texas, 226657 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - Sept. 26, 2008: Pro-Mark Drumsticks, Houston / Colorado River Tour, Burnet / Model T Restorer, Burleson / Masonic Home-Part 1, Fort Worth / Masonic Home-Part 2, Fort Worth / Carroll Abbott-Mr. Wildflower, Austin / Galveston Storms & Balinese Room, 226656 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - Oct. 25, 2008: John Henry Faulk, Madisonville / Tarpon Inn, Port Aransas / Nimitz Museum, Fredericksburg / Ray Miller, Obit, 226655 (Folder -, Episode --)
- 2009 episodes, 226649
  - KPRC's summary of 2009 episodes, 226653 (Folder 19)
  - Feb. 28, 2009: Opal Hunt-Merchant, Bradshaw / Gutzon & Lincoln Borglum- Sculptors, San Antonio / San Jacinto Monument, La Porte / Polo on the Prarie - For MD Anderson, Albany / Kreuz's & Smitty's Markets - BBQ Kings, Lockhart / Honey Creek, Boerne / Cecil Franklin - Bluesman, Nacogdoches, 226652 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - May 29, 2009: Bonnie & Clyde, Dallas / Robert Bruno House, Lubbock / NASA, Johnson Space Center, Houston / NASA, Journey to the Moon / Gary James / John Jackson-Basket Maker, Punkin / Caddo and LBJ Grasslands, Bonham and Decatur, 226651 (Folder -, Episode --)
  - August 28, 2009: Spoetzl Brewery/Shiner Beer, Shiner / Lacy Dogs, Marble Falls / Gussie Nell Davis - Kilgore Rangerettes, Kilgore / Weaver Bees, Navasota / Lynchburg Ferry, Lynchburg to La Porte / James Lee Baltimore, Kirbyville / Cool Globes, Houston, 226650 (Folder -, Episode --)